<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ChaandTaaraFoodRider</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="basket">Basket</string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="user">User</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="conditions">1. Individuals, aged 18 years or above can make a purchase from Chaand Taara Food Rider.\n\n2. Customer will need an active email address and a telephone number which can be used for making a contact as necessary.\n\n3. Customer takes the responsibility of maintaining the confidentiality of his/her account details including password and preventing unauthorised access to his/her account.\n\n4. Customer is solely responsible for providing the correct billing and delivery addresses.\n\n5. Delivery will take place at the delivery address specified by customer during the ordering process.\n\n6. Orders can only be cancelled before the goods are dispatched, by notifying the seller in writing.\n\n7. All goods, items or offers shown on our catalogue are subjected to availability at any given time and may not be ready in our stock at all the time.\n\n8. In case customer decides to cancel an order, we reserve the right to charge the applicable transaction charges.\n\n9. Order with incomplete payment or non-payment shall be on hold until a complete payment is made. In case such orders are not paid with at the time of delivery, they shall be automatically cancelled and the cancellation charges shall apply.\n\n9. We reserve the right to adjust prices, goods and special offers at our discretion.\n\n10. We carry the right to modify or discontinue any or all products at any point of time, with or without any prior notice, temporarily or permanently. We bear no liability for any such modification, suspension or discontinuance of any product or services.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottom_navigation">BottomNavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
</resources>